airastana.com 2016-12-29

# Privacy Policy

Air Astana is committed to protecting privacy of its customers.

Great care is taken with personal information that is provided to Air Astana through our website, taking steps to keep it secure and ensure it is used only for legitimate purposes.

We will never wilfully disclose personal information about you to any third party other than to process your order without first receiving your permission or unless we are under a legal obligation to do so.

You can always enquire about or check the information that you have given us by contacting us.

### Data protection

We take necessary measures for the protection of the data against wrongful access, change, disclosing or destruction. This includes internal check of processes of gathering, storage and data processing and security measures, and also measures on maintenance of physical safety of the data for prevention of wrongful access to systems in which we store the personal data.

We give access to the personal data only those workers, contractors and agents of Air Astana whom this information is necessary for operation, development and improvement of our services. These persons are contractually obliged to maintain the confidentiality of this information.

### Security policy

To ensure the security of your personal data information when you book flights through www.airastana.com, SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) with 128 Bit encryption technology is used to transfer your data securely. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit/debit card number, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet.

If your browser does not support SSL, we recommend you to update to the latest version of any browser to improve the security of transactions, otherwise the transmission of your personal information may not be protected and Air Astana disclaims any responsibility in this regard. 

### Email services

When you subscribe to receiving such communications as Air Astana’s electronic newsletter, you are giving Air Astana permission to use your email address for sending you the newsletter, and other mail such as surveys and news about special offers. You can subscribe to electronic newsletters via our Frequent Flyer Programme Nomad Club **** or on Subscribe to Specials Offers page at airastana.com.

If you wish to retract your permission for Air Astana and do not want to receive information by email, you can do so any time by clicking the ‘unsubscribe’ link at the bottom of the email.

### Cookie Policy

A cookie is a small piece of information sent from a website and temporarily stored in a user’s web browser. The browser then returns the cookie to the server the next time the page is referenced. Cookies allow a website to customize a visit and give you a better user experience when you return to the website.

Airastana.com uses cookies for collecting information about how visitors use airastana.com, for remembering visitor preferences (eg. country, language), and visitor profiling for retargeting purposes. Tracking is done anonymously and no personal information about you can be scanned or retrieved.

By visiting airastana.com you agree that Air Astana places cookies on your device.

### Contact

For enquiries or complaints about the protection of your personal information by Air Astana, please email [customer.relations@airastana.com](mailto:customer.relations@airastana.com) and we will contact you as soon as possible.

To view your personal information, have it corrected or submit a complaint about the use of your personal information by Air Astana, you may send your written response, accompanied by a copy of your proof of identity, to:

Air Astana JSC  
Customer Relations  
4A, Zakarpatskaya Str.  
Almaty 050039  
Kazakhstan  
+7 727 258 41 36
